

Murad Muradov

Front-End Developer

I'm a Vue.js developer trying to achieve a fast and creative experience in the front-end world. Adhering to design standards, I manage to create modern and responsive websites. Latest web I am very interested in following trends and taking advantage of technologies. Creative and functional web creating apps is a motivation for me and enhances my experience. Even more in every project I have a willingness to learn and develop.

m.muradmuradov@gmail.com

💡 Baku, Azerbaijan

in linkedin.com/in/m-muradmuradov

+994 51 540 95 61

muradmuradov.netlify.app

github.com/muradmuradov987

WORK EXPERIENCE

DOST Digital Innovations Center Frontend Developer

08/2022 - Present

Job description

- Creating and developing new projects with vue js
- Work with QA team to resolve reported bugs to work
- A diary to provide updates about the project participating in stand-ups
- Providing the existing project with new functionality

Meetsoft LLCFrontend Developer

08/2021 - 08/2022

Job description

- Providing technical support to existing projects
- Writing the code of the designed site
- Implementation of tasks given in this field

SKILLS

HTML CSS SASS Bootstrap Javascript

Jquery Vue Pinia Git Github Figma

EDUCATION

Mingachevir State University
Management and organization of Industry
2016 - 2021

Baku State Economic and Humanities College

Traffic Policeman specialist

2009 - 2013